articles.com.my 2010-11-20

# Free Web Site Content | Articles Submission Directory

Privacy Policy

**Subscription Forms**  
My Articles uses subscription forms for individuals to request information by subscribing to Email Newsletters based on their categories of interest. We collect visitor's contact information (like your email address) to provide you with the information that you request. We will periodically send you email referring to news and updates of Articles.com.my.

**Opt-In**  
We provide opt-in opportunities for all email lists that you choose to receive. We use your email addresses to confirm your subscription and validity of the provided email address. Your reply to this email is necessary for completing your subscription to any email list.

**IP address**  
We use your IP address, browser type, domain names, and access times, operating system, country of origin, page views, and users sessions to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer our Web site. Your IP, etc. address is used to gather broad demographic information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer. Our site only uses session ID cookies so our advertisement server can deliver proper ad rotation sequences. For example, if three banners are in rotation, the individual gets the proper rotation without duplicates. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to personally identifiable information while on our site. Further, once a user closes their browser the cookie simply terminates.

**Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. My Articles is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. My Articles recommends you refer to each Network Member's Privacy Statements.

**Sharing Information**  
My Articles does not share, sell or rent your email addresses to outside third parties. Personally identifiable information will only be disclosed due to law or court demands.

**Supplementation of Information**  
We do not supplement your personally identifiable information with any outside third parties information.

**Correct / Update**  
Change the email address that you have subscribed with by first unsubscribing with your current email address. Then, resubscribe with your new email address. All email list welcome messages contain the information necessary for subscription and removal from their appropriate list.

**Unsubscribe**  
We provide unsubscribe/opt-out opportunities for all email lists that you choose to receive. All email list welcome messages contain the information necessary for removal from the list. Removal from all lists is instant and automated by our servers.

**Notification of Changes**  
My Articles will occasionally update our Privacy Policy based on our employees' and users' feedback. If there are any material changes to how we use your personal information, we will notify via email and provide you the opportunity to opt-out prior to any substantial change that has been taken. However, if you have opted out of all communication from Articles.com.my you will not be contacted, nor will your personal information be used in this new manner. My Articles encourages you to periodically review our privacy policy to be informed of how we are committed to protecting your privacy.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our Web site.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can email us **admin at articles.com.my**
